Okay, so I'm here in Cursor and it's
ready for yolo time. You don't need to
be in cursor. You can be in whichever
one of the idees that you liked. But if
you want to stick with me, then stay in
cursor. We'll do this together. And you
I've gone to file and gone to new window
and I'm going to press open project and
I'm going to go into my projects and I'm
going to create a new folder. I'm
calling it site sit for website. I go
into it. Here we are inside site. I
press open. And now we're in project
site. You know it because site is in
block capitals. There we are ready to
build this. Okay. Next up I'm going to
do something very carefully and you are
too. You're going to be very careful
here. Here in site you're going to
rightclick and say new file. And I'm
going to call this file exactly dot the
dot and then env.
And it needs to be called exactly that
or things won't work for you. So it has
to be right. And what you put in here
has to be also exactly correct. Open
router one word open routter_appi_key
equals and then something to be pasted
in here. What do we paste in here? What
we paste in here is something that we
take from here that the API key that
we've got right here in open router. You
remember this? You copied it to the
clipboard before. If in doubt, create a
new key and copy it to the clipboard.
So, you've definitely got a key copied
to your clipboard. And then you come
back here and you do paste. And the key
appears there. And now you have an open
router API key that is in here. And this
white blob up here means that this file
hasn't yet been saved. So, this isn't
yet stored to disk. I'm going to save it
with command S on a Mac, control S on a
PC, or file save. And then the blob goes
away. And this is now saved. It's
spelled open router_appi_key
equals and then the key is in there. If
you're using an open AI key direct, it's
open AAI API key. You have to get this
right, otherwise it won't work. So very
important to get this right. Okay, next
up, right click here, new file. We're
going to create another file. So I'm
going to do that again. Right click, new
file, and then I'm going to do
ignore. All one word like that. Git
ignore. Uh, and this is where you list
the names of files that should never get
put into git. Uh, and we're going to
list one file, and it's the file that is
called.EMV.
And I now save that. And this just means
even though this isn't actually, we
haven't made a git repository for this.
If we ever do in the future, it will
make sure that this file is never added
to the repository, which is always good,
best practice, good thing to do. Make
sure that yourv file is mentioned in
your.git ignore. Okay, that's just some
some setup. We've got our key here.
Let's let's move forwards. All right,
next up, I have gone to my LinkedIn
page. Here it is. This is my LinkedIn
page. And I am now going to go here to
resources and go to save to PDF so that
I can save my profile. This is on my
profile page as a PDF. Now, this feature
might not be available to everyone
because LinkedIn is is funny and changes
things from time to time, and it might
only be available to a subset. If you
can't save your PDF of your profile,
just copy and paste the text of it into
a text file. Or if you've got a PDF of
your resume, your CV, use that instead.
Whatever you've got. I've done that.
I've saved it to PDF. And then I'm going
to move that file into this this uh this
project directory as well. Okay. Next
up, bring up the cursor settings. You
can do it from the menus or you can do
uh control shiftJ on a PC, command
shiftJ on a Mac. Up they come. Here we
have it. We're going to start by going
to the agents area. A few things to
check for the usage summary. Change this
if it's on auto to always. And then it
tells you at the bottom how much of your
plan you've used in terms of of the
models. uh scroll down here and get to
the section that is called auto run
which is the yolo section and if that's
set to ask every time or to auto run in
sandbox change it to run everything
unsandboxed assuming you're comfortable
with this if you're not of course keep
it on approving it step by step if in
doubt have it on a mode where you get to
agree to everything as you see it but
today I at least am going to be yoloing
so I leave that on run everything.
Finally, I'm going to the models tab
myself. I am going to turn on GPT 5.2
codeex high. I want to use the really
strong version of codecs. Uh so that's
what I'm choosing. You can pick what you
want. Pick the one that you like. Um but
that is what I am going with for this
myself. It's as I say this is more
expensive, but it means we should get
higher quality. Okay, those are our
decisions. All right, now I'm closing
this. I'm going to drag this across so
we've got nice and big agent screen over
here. I'm going to change auto. Turn
that off. I'm going to say I want GPT52
codeex high. That's what we want. And
I'm going to paste in here my
instruction. Now, of course, the right
approach is to write an agents.md
and and then to to work hard on giving
it all of the right information. But we
are on complete yolo mode where we're
just going to fire off an instruction
and let the agent do its thing. Tomorrow
we're going to be more disciplined and
follow the proper proper procedures, but
for now we're just going to go for it.
So, I'm pasting in here, please build me
a professional website running locally.
My LinkedIn profile is in linkedin. PDF.
Make the website stunning. Enterprise
meets edgy. It should include about me,
my career journey, links to a portfolio
for future. Iterate to make it as slick
and professional as possible and let me
know when complete. Use nextJS. That's
it. That's the instruction. That is what
we are giving GPT 5.2 codeex high. All
right. I kick this off and off goes our
agent. It's planning its moves. Uh so
it's going to uh now start doing its
thing. I think we'll see what happens.
It's going to have problems running that
in the root directory. We'll see how it
navigates its way through various
problems. And yeah, it's created a
subdirectory for me called web, which is
great. Good for it. Uh we will let it do
its thing. And I will see you in a few
minutes. It may take a while. It may
mean need to go and get another coffee.
Uh I will see you when it's wrapped up
and we will see what kind of website we
have at the end of it. Okay. So it
believes it is finished. It says it's
built a polished enterprise meets edgy
next.js site in web using your LinkedIn
content. All right. You ready to try
this out? I'm going to open up the
terminal. You can go to to view terminal
in cursor. I'm going to do it with
control back tick. Here it is. I'll give
myself a little bit more room. It tells
me to cd into web and it tells me to do
mpm rundev. Is this going to work? Let's
find out. Here we go. Well, it appears
to have come up there. Now I will bring
up a browser window. You're getting like
realtime reaction here. Local host 3000.
Let's see what we get.
That's not much good. All right. Back we
go. Back we go here. Uh that um um I
will I will stop this over here. Um that
uh hang on.
We can just copy all of this like this.
I can just take all of this. I can copy
it. I don't even need to give an
explanation. I can just paste that in
there and just press enter. We are
vibing. We are yoloing. We're not going
to even bother explaining ourselves. We
just send it the error and we say, "Come
on, make it work." All right, I'll see
you in a next sec. Well, the next sec
literally was a sack. It just sort of
finished, made a tiny change. You'll
notice again a clear sign. It didn't
prove that was the problem. It hasn't
proved it's fixed it. It says the page
should render. Of course, what we should
do is have an agents.md that insists do
not say you fixed something unless
you've proven it. But, nonetheless,
we're just going to keep going here. I'm
just going to do an mpm rundev again.
Let that thing come up. I'm going to
come over here. I'm going to try running
my website. Let's see what we get. Okay.
Okay. First impression positive. I like
this. I like it a lot. I like the way it
looks. I like this this branding. I
didn't tell it anything about the colors
or anything, but I got to tell you, I
think it does look quite enterprise
meets edgy. All right, let's take a look
at this. I'm making it fill up all of
here. Here. Let me make this nice and
big so you see it the way I see it. Very
nice. Okay. So, we've got uh we've got
like this this nice little title here
which looks very nicely done. There's
about me. This is nice summary for my
LinkedIn profile. There we go. Career
journey. It's all Oh, look. It gets
darker. That's kind of cool. Portfolio
coming soon. And there's uh there's
stuff in here. Uh let's build the
future. Book a conversation. connect on
LinkedIn. I wonder where these things
go. I that just sends an an email uh to
me uh to my it's got my real email
address in there from my LinkedIn
profile. And this uh is just a link to
my LinkedIn. So So first at first blush,
this is pretty impressive. It's a nice
functioning website being served on
local host. We'll we'll give uh we'll
try out some more things. All right,
let's check what these things do. What
happens if I press career? Oh, it comes
all the way down to my career journey in
this nice dark black. That's nice.
portfolio. Wee takes you to the uh to
the portfolio. Okay, got it. Portfolio
hub. What is that? Uh that just takes me
over to my personal web page. How about
that? That's clever of it. That links to
my uh to to my own uh website. There it
comes up on a separate page. Nice. Very
nice. Uh let's talk. I can see that's
going to open my email program and email
to my email address that is on my
LinkedIn profile. So, it grabbed that.
It's really nice. signature work,
current focus. I'd say this is a great
website. The only thing it's missing is
some functionality. Let's give it some
functionality.